Katrina Sarmiento

■ ksarmiento020@gmail.com

514-582-0120

Igaluit, NU, Canada, X0A 0H0

| Starmiento020@gmail.com

| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Starmiento020@gmail.com
| Sta

PROFILE

I have extensive experience in providing confidential administrative support to high-profile organizations. My expertise includes agenda preparation, document management, travel coordination, and event planning. With excellent organizational skills and attention to detail, I am efficient in delivering results.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Executive Assistant

11/2020 - present | Igaluit, NU, Canada

City of Igaluit

- Provide confidential administrative support to the Mayor, City Council, and City Administration.
- Assist in agenda preparation for Council, Committee of the Whole, and Senior management meetings.
- Coordinate travel arrangements for key city personnel.
- Manage document distribution and filing.
- Maintain an up-to-date calendar of events on the City website.
- Ensure accurate and timely posting of Minutes, By-Laws, and other documents.

HUB Intake Coordinator (Project Contract)

08/2020 - 11/2021Igaluit, NU, Canada

Qikiqtaaluk Corporation

Scheduled medical and public traveler appointments.

- Coordinated with hotels for accommodations.
- Managed isolation traveler information and database.
- Produced daily reports.

Administrative Support (Part-time)

09/2020 - 03/2021

Igaluit, NU, Canada

- Law Society of Nunavut
- Supported RAC and Certificate of Standing applications.
- Updated Membership Status Reports and Law Society website content.
- · Drafted various documents.

Inventory Clerk 06/2019 - 03/2020

Ciara Technologies

Montreal, QC, Canada

- Oversaw parts inventory, transfers, and documentation.
- · Maintained daily transaction records.
- Processed client orders and supported field technicians.

Senior Internal Auditor / Junior Internal Auditor

04/2013 - 05/2018 Manila, Philippines

Executive Optical

• Supervised Junior Auditors, providing guidance and reviewing deliverables.

- Conducted inventory count cycles, ensuring accuracy.
- · Communicated tasks clearly and efficiently.
- Reconciled inventory variances and prepared detailed reports.
- · Ensured audit conclusions were well-founded.

EDUCATION

International Commerce- Import and Export (FITT) -Certificate

2018 - 2019 | Montreal, Philippines

Collège LaSalle, Montréal

Bachelor of Science in Commerce major in Internal Auditing

2009 - 2013 | Manila, Philippines

Far Eastern University

SKILLS

- Document & Database Management
- Inventory Control
- Multitasking and prioritization
- Strong organizational and time management skills

- Administrative Support, Confidentiality and discretion
- Calendar Management & Travel Coordination
- Attention to detail and accuracy

CERTIFICATES

- Supervisor Familiarization for Northwest Territories and Nunavut
- Heart & Stroke Standard First Aid